<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="14"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Written by:
                                                                                Sarra Ben Amara]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[About:









         The Hidden Portal is a delightful collection of tales that will captivate both children

         and adults alike. Through a series of charming and whimsical stories, readers will

         embark on a journey of adventure and wonder, exploring imaginative worlds filled

         with magic, mystery, and heart. Each tale features a unique cast of characters, from

         brave heroes and heroines to mischievous animals and wise elders, all of whom

         will inspire and enchant readers with their bravery, kindness, and wit. Whether

         read aloud or savored alone, The Hidden Portal is a treasure trove of storytelling


         that will leave readers smiling, dreaming, and eager for more.
















                                   www.onlinetutorschool.com]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Once upon a time, there were three siblings named Sarah, Mark, and Lily. They

         lived in a small town surrounded by woods, and they loved to explore the outdoors

         together. One day, while wandering through the woods, they stumbled upon a

         mysterious cave they had never seen before.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Curious, they ventured inside and discovered a glowing portal that shimmered with a

        rainbow of colors. Without hesitation, the siblings stepped through the portal, and

        suddenly found themselves transported to a world of magic and wonder.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[As they explored this new world, they encountered all sorts of magical creatures,


      including unicorns, dragons, and talking trees. They marveled at the beauty of the land,

      with its sparkling rivers and fields of flowers. They were amazed by the kindness of the

      creatures they met, who welcomed them with open arms.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[The siblings soon realized that they had stumbled upon a world that had been hidden

      away from humans for centuries. They knew that they had to keep it a secret, to protect

      the magical creatures from those who might harm them.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[As they journeyed through this new world, they learned new skills and gained the trust


      of the creatures they encountered. Sarah became an expert at communicating with the

      unicorns, while Mark learned to tame and ride the mighty dragons. Lily, with her gentle

      touch, was able to heal injured creatures and mend broken hearts.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[But as they were enjoying their adventure, they discovered that an evil sorcerer was

        planning to destroy this magical world and all its inhabitants. The siblings knew they had

        to act fast and rallied their new friends to join forces against the sorcerer.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Together, they fought bravely, using their new skills and abilities to defeat the sorcerer's


      minions and protect the magical world. Finally, they confronted the sorcerer himself,

      and with a burst of magical energy, they vanquished him.]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[The siblings knew that their time in this magical world had come to an end, and they


      bid farewell to their new friends. As they stepped through the portal back to their own

      world, they knew they would never forget the amazing adventure they had shared and

      the bonds they had formed with the magical creatures they had met.]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[From that day on, the siblings always looked back on their adventure with wonder and


      amazement. And they knew that whenever they needed a bit of magic in their lives, they

      could close their eyes and remember the world they had discovered together.]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[All rights reserved: www.onlinetutorschool.com]]></page></pages></Search>